(Girl(arriving):)- I think you're just brilliant.
- Well, that is the prevailing opinion.
God, now I'm gonna throw up.
(Howard:)Howard Wolowitz,
Department of Engineering...
(Howard:)...co-designer of the International Space
Station's liquid-waste-disposal system.
(Howard:)Ew.
(Ramona:)Dr. Cooper, I've read everything
you've published.
I liked your paper on grand unification
using string-network condensates...
(Ramona:)...and was wondering how you determined
that three-dimensional string nets...
(Ramona:)...provided a unified picture of fermions
and gauge bosons.
(Sheldon:)Amazing. An intelligent Labradoodle.
(Howard:)Woof.
(Sheldon:)The fact is,
I'm quite close to a breakthrough...
(Sheldon:)...in showing how neutrinos emerge
from a string-net condensate.
(Ramona:)Oh, my God. That would change the way
we view the entire physical universe.
(Sheldon:)It's what I do.
(Howard:)You know, the Pishkin-Wolowitz
liquid-waste-disposal system...
(Howard:)...is turning a few heads as well.